A Guide to the Press Office Records of Virginia Governor George F. Allen, 1993-1998
Library of Virginia
- Series I. News Summaries, 1994-1998., Extent: 25 cubic feet. (Box 1-25)
  - 1997.
    - April 1-3. (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - April 4-7. (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - April 8-9. (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - April 10. (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - April 11. (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - April 12-13. (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - April 14-16. (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - April 17. (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - April 18. (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - April 19-22. (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - April 23-24. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - April 25-27. (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - April 28-30. (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - VPS Clips, April. (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - VPS Clips, April. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - VPS Clips, April. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - May 1-2. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - May 3-6. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - May 7. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - May 8-9. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - May 10-12. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - May 13. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - May 14-16. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - May 17-19. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - May 20-22. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - May 23-24. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - May 25-27. (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - May 28. (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - May 29-31. (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - VPS Clips, May. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - VPS Clips, May. (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - VPS Clips, May. (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - June 1-3. (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - June 4-5. (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - June 6. (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - June 7-9. (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - June 10. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - June 11-12. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - June 13-15. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - June 16-18. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - June 19-21. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - June 22-24. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - June 25-26. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - June 27-30. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - VPS Clips, June. (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - July 1-2. (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - July 3. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - July 4-7. (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - July 8-9. (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - July 10. (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - July 11. (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - July 12-14. (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - July 15-16. (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - July 17-20. (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - July 21-22. (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - July 23-25. (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - July 26-29. (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - July 30-31. (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - VPS Clips, July. (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - VPS Clips, July. (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - VPS Clips, July. (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - August 1-4. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - August 5-6. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - August 7-9. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - August 10-11. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - August 12. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - August 13-15. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - August 16-19. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - August 20. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - August 21-22. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - August 23-25. (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - August 26. (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - August 27-28. (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - August 29-31. (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - VPS Clips, August. (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - VPS Clips, August. (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - VPS Clips, August. (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - VPS Clips, August. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - September 1-4. (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - September 5-8. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - September 9-10. (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - September 11-12. (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - September 13-15. (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - September 16-17. (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - September 18-19. (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - September 20-22. (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - September 23-24. (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - September 25-27. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - September 28-30. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - VPS Clips, September. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - VPS Clips, September. (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - October 1-4. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - October 5-7. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - October 8-10. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - October 11-14. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - October 15-18. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - October 19-21. (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - October 22-24. (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - October 25-29. (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - October 30-31. (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - VPS Clips, October. (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - VPS Clips, October. (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - November 1-2. (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - November 3-4. (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - November 5. (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - November 6-7. (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - November 8-11. (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - November 12-14. (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - November 15-17. (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - November 18-19. (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - November 20-23. (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - November 24-26. (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - November 29-30. (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - VPS Clips, November. (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - VPS Clips, November. (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - December 1-4. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - December 5-7. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - December 8-9. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - December 10-11. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - December 12-13. (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - December 14-16. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - December 17-18. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - December 19. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - December 20-23. (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - December 24-27. (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - December 28-31. (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - VPS Clips, December. (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - VPS Clips, December. (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - 1998.
    - January 3-5. (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - January 6-7. (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - January 8-10. (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - January 11-12. (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - January 13-14. (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - January 15-16. (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - VPS Clips, January. (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Series II. Photographs, 1993-1998., Extent: 5.4 cubic feet. (Box 26-37)
  (Accessions 35863 and 43396). Contains photographs that document the events of activities of the Allen Administration. Also included are photographs of Election Night 1993 and the inauguration of Governor Jim Gilmore in January 1998. The photographs document Governor Allen's inauguration, press conferences, announcements, his RV tours of the state, trade missions to various countries, groundbreakings, ribbon cuttings, school visits and graduations, swearings-in, agency head meetings, award ceremonies, and the annual state Christmas tree lighting and Executive Mansion open house. Also included are photographs of certain activities of the first family and First Lady Susan Allen. The photographs are numbered, and most photographs were taken by Richard L. Piermarini. Folder lists containing the identification numbers can be found inside each box. An asterisk after the folder title indicates that the name of the photographer was not marked on the original envelope. The numbers and asterisks are not included in the folder list below. Included at the end of Box 37 is a folder of miscellaneous negatives and contact sheets of Allen administration photographs taken by Pierre Courtois, photographer of the Library of Virginia.
  Arrangement is loosely chronological.
  - 1993.
    - Election Night, 1993. (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
  - 1994.
    - Inauguration Day: First Lady's Luncheon, 1994 January 15. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Inauguration Day: Governor's Hoe Down, 1994 January 15. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Inauguration Day: Monticello, 1994 January 15. (Box 26, Folder 5-8)
    - Inauguration Day: State Capitol, 1994 January 15. (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Inauguration Day: State Capitol (Mrs. Allen and Children), 1994 January 15. (Box 26, Folder 10-11)
    - Inauguration Day: State Capitol (Govenor Wilder and Governor Allen), 1994 January 15. (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Inauguration Day: Inauguration at State Capitol, 1994 January 15. (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Inauguration Day: State Capitol (Governor Allen, Lt. Gov. Beyer and Attorney General Gilmore), 1994 January 15. (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Inauguration Day: Swearing-in, 1994 January 15. (Box 26, Folder 15-16)
    - Inauguration Day: State Capitol, 1994 January 15. (Box 26, Folder 17-18)
    - Inauguration Day: Inaugural Parade, 1994 January 15. (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Inauguration Day: State Capitol, 1994 January 15. (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Inauguration Day: Swearing-in, 1994 January 15. (Box 26, Folder 21-24)
    - Inauguration Day: Greeting Crowd at State Capitol, 1994 January 15. (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Inauguration Day: Entering Executive Mansion, 1994 January 15. (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Inauguration Day: Inaugural Ball (Govenor and Mrs. Allen), 1994 January 15. (Box 26, Folder 27-28)
    - First Lady's Cultural Exchange Mission to South Africa, 1994. (Box 26, Folder 29-31)
    - Former President George Bush at the Executive Mansion, 1994. (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - State Visit to Diggstown, 1994 January 21. (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Governor's Commission on Citizen Empowerment, 1994. (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - First Bill Signing, 1994 February 15. (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Swearing in of the ABC Commissioner, 1994 February 2. (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Governor Allen at Chicken's for Lunch, 1994 February 25. (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Governor Allen at Renegades Hockey Game, 1994 February 28. (Box 26, Folder 38-40)
    - VRS Bill Signing, 1994 February 28. (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - VCU Gym: Governor's Administration vs. Lobbyists Basketball Game, 1994 March 1. (Box 26, Folder 42-43)
    - Page's Breakfast, 1994 March 2. (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Bill Signing: Governor Allen with Delegate Allen Dudley, 1994 March 4. (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Photo Opportunity: Governor Allen with Delegate Bob Purkey, 1994 March 4. (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Bill Signing: Governor Allen with Delegate Frank Hargrove, 1994 March 4. (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - Certification of Landscape Architects, 1994 March 7. (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - Photo Opportunity: Governor Allen with 3rd Year Law Practice, 1994 March 7. (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - Bill Signing: Mine Safety Act, 1994 March 7. (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Photo Opportunity: Nursing Examination, 1994 March 8. (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - Bill Signing: Nursing Facility Construction Moratorium, 1994 March 8. (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - Signing Ceremony: Flunkbusters Month, 1994 March 8. (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - Bill Signing: HB266 Governor Allen with Delegate Julia Connally, 1994 March 10. (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - Bill Signing: HB1094 Governor Allen with Delegate Orrock, 1994 March 10. (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - Bill Signing: HB83 Governor Allen with Delegate Bob Tata, 1994 March 10. (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - Bill Signing: HB127 Legislative Aid, 1994 March 10. (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - Bill Signing: HB127 Governor Allen with Delegate Leo Waldrup, 1994 March 10. (Box 26, Folder 58)
    - Bill Signing: Governor Allen with Delegate George Heilig, 1994 March 11. (Box 26, Folder 59)
    - Governor Allen at Virginia Tech Graduation, 1994 May 14. (Box 26, Folder 60)
    - Governor and Mrs. Allen with Emperor and Empress of Japan, 1994 June 15. (Box 26, Folder 61)
    - Governor Allen on a Horse in the Crozet Parade, 1994 July 4. (Box 26, Folder 62)
    - NAFTA Trip Contract Award Announcement, 1994 July 9. (Box 26, Folder 63)
    - Virginia is for Lovers, 1994 September 10. (Box 26, Folder 64-65)
    - Bill Signing: HB496 Governor Allen with Delegate Tata, 1994 March 12. (Box 26, Folder 66)
    - Bill Signing: HB421, 1994 March 12. (Box 26, Folder 67)
    - Photo Opportunity: Governor Allen with Delegate Joe Johnson, 1994 March 12. (Box 26, Folder 68)
    - Bedford Town Charter (Conference Room), 1994 March 16. (Box 26, Folder 69-70)
    - CIT Board Meeting, 1994 March 15. (Box 26, Folder 71)
    - Blue Ribbon Strike Force Meeting, 1994 March 18. (Box 26, Folder 72-73)
    - Photo Opportunity: Access Unlimited Picture Presentation, 1994 March 23. (Box 26, Folder 74)
    - Easter Seals, 1994 March 24. (Box 26, Folder 75)
    - Congressional Delegation Meeting, 1994 March 28. (Box 26, Folder 76)
    - Bill Signing: Virginia Beach, 1994 April 5. (Box 26, Folder 77-78)
    - Prevent Blindness (Conference Room), 1994 April 6. (Box 26, Folder 79)
    - Photo Opportunity: Save America, 1994 April 6. (Box 26, Folder 80)
    - Photo Opportunity: Delegate Jack Rollison, III., 1994 April 6. (Box 26, Folder 81)
    - Bill Signing: Crime and DUI with Kenneth Stolle, 1994 April 6. (Box 26, Folder 82)
    - Disney Signing Ceremony, 1994 April 12. (Box 26, Folder 83-85)
    - Richmond Braves Game, First Pitch, 1994 April 12. (Box 26, Folder 86)
    - Richmond Braves Game, Signing Autographs, 1994 April 12. (Box 26, Folder 87)
    - Third District Loyalty Proclamation, 1994 April 14. (Box 26, Folder 88)
    - Egg Council of Virginia, 1994 April 20. (Box 26, Folder 89-91)
    - Governor Allen at the Circus, 1994. (Box 26, Folder 92)
    - Bill Signing: DUI, 1994 April 20. (Box 26, Folder 93)
    - Photo Opportunity: Delegate Bob Harris and Jerry Kilgore, 1994 April 20. (Box 26, Folder 94)
    - Railroads (Conference Room), 1994 April 20. (Box 26, Folder 95)
    - Accident and Sickness Insurance/Bone Marrow Transplants, 1994 April 20. (Box 26, Folder 96-97)
    - Authority of Localities to Move Buildings, 1994 April 20. (Box 26, Folder 98)
    - Bill Signing: SB520 (Conference Room), 1994 April 20. (Box 26, Folder 99)
    - Jails: Medical Treatment Program, 1994 April 20. (Box 26, Folder 100)
    - Virginia Historical Documents (Conference Room), 1994 April 20. (Box 26, Folder 101)
    - HIV Testing and Release of Test Results for Good Samaritans, 1994 April 20. (Box 26, Folder 102)
    - Governor Allen with Students, 1994. (Box 26, Folder 103)
    - Registered Limited Liability Partnerships, 1994 April 21. (Box 26, Folder 104)
    - Bill Signing: HB819 (Conference Room), 1994 April 21. (Box 26, Folder 105)
    - Taxidermy (Conference Room), 1994 April 21. (Box 26, Folder 106)
    - Higher Education Tuition Trust Fund, 1994 April 21. (Box 26, Folder 107)
    - Volvo/GM Press Conference, 1994 April 29. (Box 26, Folder 108-109)
    - Speed Limits (Conference Room), 1994 May 2. (Box 26, Folder 110)
    - Gov. of Saitama (Meeting in Conference Room), 1994 May 2. (Box 26, Folder 111-113)
    - Nurses Week Proclamation Signing, 1994 May 4. (Box 26, Folder 114)
    - Safe Boating Week Proclamation Signing, 1994 May 4. (Box 26, Folder 115)
    - President of William and Mary, 1994 May 4. (Box 26, Folder 116)
    - Citizen Empowerment Meeting, 1994 May 18. (Box 26, Folder 117)
    - Bill Signing: HB73, 1994 May 10. (Box 26, Folder 118)
    - Tobacco Farmers: HB 769, 1994 May 10. (Box 26, Folder 119)
    - Manufacturing Housing Group Proclamation Signing, 1994 May 10. (Box 26, Folder 120)
    - Special Education Press Conference, 1994 May 13. (Box 26, Folder 121-122)
    - Regional Economic Development Council Meeting, 1994 May 16. (Box 26, Folder 123)
    - Open House for Constituent Affairs, 1994 May 16. (Box 26, Folder 124)
    - Biotechnology Research Park Groundbreaking, 1994 May 17. (Box 26, Folder 125-127)
    - AAA Poster Contest Winners, 1994 May 25. (Box 26, Folder 128)
    - George Marshall Foundation Book Presentation, 1994 May 25. (Box 26, Folder 129)
    - Motorcycle Awareness Week, 1994 May 21. (Box 26, Folder 130)
    - Beacher Family Visit (Conference Room), 1994 May 31. (Box 26, Folder 131-132)
    - Westvaco Announcement, 1994 May 25. (Box 26, Folder 133)
    - Change of Command: General Thackston, 1994 June 30. (Box 26, Folder 134-135)
    - Ribbon Cutting for New Play Equipment at the Executive Mansion, 1994. (Box 26, Folder 136)
    - UVA Graduation, 1994 May 20. (Box 26, Folder 137)
    - Presentation of First Lady Portrait, 1994 July 12. (Box 26, Folder 138)
    - VMI Case: Presentation to Bob Patterson, 1994 July 12. (Box 26, Folder 139-140)
    - Blue Ribbon Strike Force Meeting, 1994. (Box 26, Folder 141)
    - Virginia is for Lovers Race Car Press Conference (Mrs. Allen), 1994 July 14. (Box 26, Folder 142-144)
    - Governor Allen with Joe Gibbs, 1994. (Box 26, Folder 145)
    - Governor Allen Speaking, 1994. (Box 26, Folder 146)
    - Governor's Fellows Reception, 1994 July 14. (Box 26, Folder 147)
    - Mayor Young's Endorsement, 1994 August 24. (Box 26, Folder 148)
    - Governor Allen and Attorney General Gilmore, 1994 August. (Box 26, Folder 149)
    - Governor Allen Inspecting Buildings, 1994 August. (Box 26, Folder 150)
    - Abolish Parole Rally (State Capitol Grounds), 1994 August 25. (Box 26, Folder 151-152)
    - Kiwanis Club/Rotary Club, 1994 September 6. (Box 26, Folder 153-154)
    - BRADA Commission Swearing-in, 1994 September 8. (Box 26, Folder 155-156)
    - Law Enforcement Endorsement, 1994 September 8. (Box 26, Folder 157-158)
    - Governor Allen with Rob Reiner During Filming of "Tad," 1994 September 12. (Box 26, Folder 159)
    - Abolish Parole Rally in front of GAB, 1994 September 19. (Box 26, Folder 160-162)
    - Victims Rally at Bell Tower, 1994 September 19. (Box 26, Folder 163-164)
    - Governor Allen Speaking to Joint Session, 1994 September 19. (Box 26, Folder 165)
    - Forrest Allen and Guest at Lunch with Governor Allen, 1994 September 26. (Box 26, Folder 166)
    - Rick Richardson: Executive Director Regional Economic, 1994 September 26. (Box 26, Folder 167)
    - Miscellaneous Meeting Photographs, 1994. (Box 26, Folder 168-169)
    - Joint Assembly in House Chamber, 1994 September 19. (Box 26, Folder 170-171)
    - State Fair/Virginia Online, 1994 September 27. (Box 26, Folder 172-173)
    - Breast Cancer Awareness Month, 1994 September 29. (Box 26, Folder 174-175)
    - Sine Dic (Special Session)/Abolish Parole, 1994 September 30. (Box 26, Folder 176)
    - Photo Opportunity: Virginia Port Authority, Norfolk, 1994 October 4. (Box 26, Folder 177-178)
    - Opening of New DMV Customer Service Center, 1994 October 6. (Box 26, Folder 179-180)
    - NASA Presentation, 1994. (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
    - Virginia Tech Football, 1994 October 11. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Altavista and Abbott, Virginia/Labor Ties, 1994 October 11. (Box 27, Folder 4-6)
    - Bill Signing: Abolish Parole (South Portico), 1994 October 13. (Box 27, Folder 7-8)
    - Character Coalition Press Conference (Reston, Virginia), 1994 October 19. (Box 27, Folder 9-11)
    - Governor Allen and Sec. of Education Beverly Sgro, 1994 October. (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Governor Allen Photographs, 1994 October. (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Governor Allen and a Hunter, 1994 October. (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Norfolk Assembly Plant Expansion, 1994 October 20. (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Pakistan Ambassador Visit, 1994 October 27. (Box 27, Folder 16-17)
    - Ambassador from Germany, 1994 October 31. (Box 27, Folder 18-19)
    - Reindeer Days at Executive Mansion, 1994 November 2. (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Good Morning America (Capitol Grounds), 1994 November 8. (Box 27, Folder 21-24)
    - Federalism Press Conference, 1994 November 14. (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - UVA-Virginia Tech Classic Football Game, 1994 November 19. (Box 27, Folder 26-28)
    - Annual Indian Tribute (Executive Mansion), 1994 November 23. (Box 27, Folder 29-32)
    - Tax Cut Announcement, 1994 December 1. (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Signing Ceremony: Sentinel Systems Contract, 1994 December 6. (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Diplomatic Ambassador's Reception (Executive Mansion), 1994 December 6. (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Christmas Tree Lighting and Open House, 1994 December 7. (Box 27, Folder 36-37)
    - Opportunity Virginia Unveiling (Omni Hotel), 1994 December 7. (Box 27, Folder 38-40)
    - Bosher's Dam Fish Passage Presention, 1994 December 16. (Box 27, Folder 41-42)
    - Governor's Office Christmas Party, 1994 December 22. (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Parole Board Press Conference/Swearing-in, 1994 February 2. (Box 27, Folder 44-45)
  - 1995.
    - Henry County Drug Grant, 1995 October 3. (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - Photo Opportunity: Baton Twirlers, 1995 January 4. (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - Birthday Party, 1995. (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Governor Harrison's Funeral (Lawrenceville, Virginia), 1995 January 25. (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - Keep Virginia Beautiful (Conference Room), 1995 February 1. (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - Photo Opportunity: Grocer of the Year Award, 1995 February 4. (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - Model General Assembly Officers, 1995 February 2. (Box 27, Folder 52)
    - Margaret Thatcher's Visit to the Executive Mansion, 1995 February 3. (Box 27, Folder 53-55)
    - Virginia Home Educator's Association, 1995 February 15. (Box 27, Folder 56)
    - Exceptional Children Week, 1995 February 15. (Box 27, Folder 57)
    - Vocational Education Week, 1995 February 15. (Box 27, Folder 58)
    - Sales and Use Tax Exemption Commerical/Media, 1995 March 8. (Box 27, Folder 59)
    - Governor Allen at Renegades Hockey Game, 1995 March 8. (Box 27, Folder 60)
    - Bill Signing: Workforce Transition Act of 1995, 1995 March 10. (Box 27, Folder 61)
    - Governor Allen at Mary Munford School, 1995 March 27. (Box 27, Folder 62-64)
    - Mrs. Allen with Unidentified Group on Executive Mansion Stairs, 1995. (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - HB2530: Distribution of Ward's Estate, 1995 April 4. (Box 27, Folder 66)
    - Bill Signing: HB1546, 1995 April 4. (Box 27, Folder 67)
    - National Auctioneer Week, 1995 April 6. (Box 27, Folder 68)
    - Model General Assembly (St. John's Church), 1995 April 7. (Box 27, Folder 69)
    - Motorcycle Awareness Week, 1995 April 10. (Box 27, Folder 70)
    - National Organ and Tissue Donor Week, 1995 April 10. (Box 27, Folder 71)
    - Yorktown Victory Center Grand Opening, 1995 April 11. (Box 27, Folder 72)
    - Virginia Winner of Interlocher Award, 1995 May. (Box 27, Folder 73)
    - Bill Signing: Uninsured Motorist Bill, 1995 May. (Box 27, Folder 74)
    - South African Delegation, 1995 May 17. (Box 27, Folder 75)
    - Federal Emergency Management Agency, 1995 May 18. (Box 27, Folder 76-77)
    - Governor Allen with Delegate Almand (Conference Room), 1995 June 20. (Box 27, Folder 78)
    - Agency Leadership Workshop, 1995 June 2. (Box 27, Folder 79)
    - Bill Signing: HB2337, 1995 June 19. (Box 27, Folder 80)
    - Freedom Award from Law Alliance of America (for SB744), 1995 June 19. (Box 27, Folder 81-82)
    - Bill Signing: HB2293, 1995 June 19. (Box 27, Folder 83)
    - Bill Signing: SB726, 1995 June 19. (Box 27, Folder 84)
    - Bill Signing: SB830, 1995 June 19. (Box 27, Folder 85)
    - Bill Signing: HB2583, 1995 June 19. (Box 27, Folder 86)
    - Bill Signing: HB768 (Conference Room), 1995 June 20. (Box 27, Folder 87)
    - Bill Signing: HB2595, 1995 June 20. (Box 27, Folder 88)
    - Bill Signing: SB858 (Conference Room), 1995 June 20. (Box 27, Folder 89)
    - Bill Signing: HB2587, 1995 June 20. (Box 27, Folder 90)
    - Bill Signing: SB828, 1995 June 20. (Box 27, Folder 91)
    - Bill Signing: HB1884, 1995 June 20. (Box 27, Folder 92)
    - Prom Promise (Botetourt), 1995 June 21. (Box 27, Folder 93)
    - Prom Promise (Tazewell High School), 1995 June 21. (Box 27, Folder 94)
    - Nationwide Insurance, 1995 June 21. (Box 27, Folder 95)
    - Battle of the Brains, 1995 June 21. (Box 27, Folder 96)
    - Ambassador from Austria (Conference Room), 1995 July 7. (Box 27, Folder 97-98)
    - FEMA Signing Press Conference (Conference Room), 1995 July 7. (Box 27, Folder 99)
    - RV Tour: Meadows of Dan, 1995 July 15. (Box 27, Folder 100)
    - RV Tour: Abingdon and Richlands, 1995 July 21. (Box 27, Folder 101)
    - RV Tour: Bristol and Richlands, 1995 July 21. (Box 27, Folder 102)
    - AAA School Safety Patrol Week, 1995 September 8. (Box 27, Folder 103)
    - Motorola, 1995 September 7. (Box 27, Folder 104)
    - Virginia Museum Luncheon, 1995 September 21. (Box 27, Folder 105)
    - Promoting Virginia History/P. Largarde's Luncheon, 1995 September 22. (Box 27, Folder 106)
    - WRVA/State Fair, 1995 September 26. (Box 27, Folder 107)
    - Rabies Awareness Week, 1995 September 26. (Box 27, Folder 108)
    - Varina All-Star Baseball Team, State Champs, 1995 September 25. (Box 27, Folder 109)